<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<articlearchive>
    <articles>
        <article>
            <articleid>1303</articleid>
            <title>Honkai: Star Rail Version 3.4 will finally introduce those Fate/stay night collab characters you've been hearing about</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/honkai-star-rail-version-3-4-new-characters</link>
            <description>The big Honkai: Star Rail version 3.4 livestream took place earlier today, right on schedule. As with every major new iteration of the incredibly popular HoYoverse game, the main thing people have been looking forward to has been, of course, the new characters. The livestream did, indeed, show off the new characters that will be arriving in the free-to-play RPG soon. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-20</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\d9048e6f-fe50-4c22-ab05-b0feacbd9467.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1304</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign now has even tougher Nightlord bosses, and a new NPC to serve those who take on the challenge</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-everdark-sovereign-enhanced-bosses-new-npc</link>
            <description>A little while ago, FromSoftware responded to the generally positive reception of Elden Ring Nightreign following the games launch, promising an official duos mode, as well as something the developer referred to as enhanced fights against existing Nightlords. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-19</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\3db4e1a1-1e19-4dc6-85a6-06236382df89.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1305</articleid>
            <title>Borderlands 4 is a bold departure for the series, but 2K may have carved off some of its soul in the pursuit of killing cringe - preview</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/borderlands-4-preview</link>
            <description>Borderlands is undergoing a grand and drastic rebirth with Borderlands 4. It's more mature, less zany than before. A smart haircut and fresh new work shirt. It's bringing with it a gameplay overhaul, taking what's loved from the hugely profitable original trilogy and adding to it a contemporary makeover. It marks a new era for Borderlands, and while it still offers that same lootin' and shootin' richness as you'd expect, I can't help but feel some meaty chunk of its soul has been thrown out the window in the attempt. 
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-18</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\articles\58042ef6-b975-4b94-822a-0a16cbd96479.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1306</articleid>
            <title>FromSoftware makes the Libra fight easier, with Elden Ring Nightreign's latest patch making Madness weapons more common</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-patch-1-01-3-full-details</link>
            <description>FromSoftware has brought Elden Ring Nightreign servers back online following three hours of maintenance that kicked off earlier today. The downtime was necessary to deploy the games latest patch, version 1.01.3, which is now available across all platforms. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-18</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\63476db4-6467-44b4-80af-7908ad652c2d.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1307</articleid>
            <title>This is why it takes too damn long to revive a downed Elden Ring Nightreign player with three segments</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-revive-system-staggering-discoveries-timer-hp</link>
            <description>Elden Ring Nightreign represents several key firsts for developer FromSoftware. As intriguing as it is to watch the studio, known for its single-player games, develop a multiplayer-only title that borrows from roguelikes and battle royale games, one has to stop and consider how the team attempted to solve certain problems. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-18</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\618d8758-7076-4d88-81b7-50770905ed59.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1308</articleid>
            <title>The next set of Monster Hunter Wilds Event Quests actually has new stuff to do, but there are still no Challenge Quests</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/monster-hunter-wilds-event-quests-late-june-early-july</link>
            <description>If you dont intend to jump into any of the new games coming out this week and for the rest of June, you might want to check in on the latest batch of Monster Hunter Wilds Event Quests. Capcom, right on schedule, has published the full stack for this week, next, and the one after that. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-18</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\cd54bc1d-6c01-48c4-82a9-250ec4e8588a.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1309</articleid>
            <title>The sinister secret that Mario Kart World is hiding: where do those Dash Foods come from?</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/mario-kart-world-sinister-secret-dash-foods</link>
            <description>Last week, I spent most of my time working on Mario Kart World, explaining to others how to unlock its roster of characters, and costumes for them to wear, among guides for other new mechanics. It was while I looked into Dash Foods  those yellow lunch bags with a tasty treat inside that have the possibility of unlocking a new costume  that I had a particularly damning realisation. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-17</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\b5ac126e-e345-4abe-a97b-ddf941a7ad9c.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1310</articleid>
            <title>Love and Deepspace's latest update introduces a new story for Rafayel, making him the first character to get a third Myth lore drop</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/love-and-deepspace-submerged-eclipse-memory-pair-event-details</link>
            <description>Today marks the start of a major new Memory Pair event in Love and Deepspace, the mobile dating sim people cant stop talking about. The new event is called Submerged Eclipse, kicks off today, and will be available until July 1. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-17</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\3c4a4db8-a76b-4c20-8b17-058f561a9da1.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1311</articleid>
            <title>Zelda: Breath of the Wild is now MetaCritic’s #1 game in 2025, and that just feels weird</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/zelda-breath-of-the-wild-metacritic-number-one-2025-clair-obscur-expedition-33</link>
            <description>The launch of the Nintendo Switch 2 has caused a bit of a disturbance in the rankings of games released this year, as far as the overall critical score is concerned. The reason is fairly standard, and it has to do with older games being re-released for the new console. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-16</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\a90e68b9-6c13-4458-930c-082aac889c7b.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1312</articleid>
            <title>Nintendo Switch 2 users create superlist of games that have seen significant technical improvements</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/nintendo-switch-2-users-create-superlist-of-games-that-have-seen-significant-technical-improvements</link>
            <description>Nintendo Switch 2 users have compiled a massive list of original Switch games playable on the new console, as well as the technical improvements present if players boot them up on newer hardware. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-16</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\c4aea3a2-be92-496b-aae0-9f419d3e180b.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1313</articleid>
            <title>Look how many of Elden Ring Nightreign’s skins reference classic Dark Souls characters, and how much better they look here</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-dark-souls-skins-comparison</link>
            <description>Even before anyone was able to get their hands on Elden Ring Nightreign, we knew that it would bring back bosses, enemies, characters and more from classic FromSoftware games - including the Dark Souls series. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-16</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\c3e9c7ba-c9d7-4d17-bf2f-06887cc906ae.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1314</articleid>
            <title>Silent Hill revival is far from over, with the original 1999 cult classic finally being remade</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/silent-hill-revival-is-far-from-over-original-being-remade</link>
            <description>Off the back of the success of the Silent Hill 2 Remake  a remake that blew my initial low expectations out of the water completely  Konami has announced that it is working with Bloober Team once more to remake the original Silent Hill from 1999. We dont yet have a release window, however, with the game being announced as in development from Bloober Team and Konami, with no additional details. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-13</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\79eaaff8-ade7-4b37-9ed0-e83a273ae196.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1315</articleid>
            <title>inZOI is on sale for the first time to celebrate the big June update</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/inzoi-first-sale-steam-big-june-update</link>
            <description>It seems like things are getting exciting in the world of inZOI once again, after what felt like months of no comms and some patch delays. Earlier this week, the team behind the life sim finally announced a release date for its next update. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-13</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\23fe5400-a920-4420-83bf-604b17553d2e.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1316</articleid>
            <title>The Sims 4 Enchanted by Nature gets an official reveal trailer confirming that fairies are so back</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/the-sims-4-enchanted-by-nature-reveal-trailer</link>
            <description>Our first look at Enchanted by Nature, the new expansion coming to The Sims 4 next month, has officially arrived. Maxis and EA previously confirmed that the first trailer would be dropping today, before we get a deep look at gameplay on June 26. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-12</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\17ac3892-d52b-4ef1-9bc9-2eec6082131a.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1317</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign players have created the ultimate cheat sheet for the weaknesses and resistances of every Nightlord</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-nightlord-weaknesses-resistances-chart</link>
            <description>Elden Ring Nightreign has been out for just under two weeks now. Usually, thats enough time for some prevailing strategies - and clever discoveries - to emerge. Because of the way the game is structured, however, its not always easy to replicate your experience, which makes it a lot more difficult to pin down those things. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-12</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\60b5997f-cdab-42ff-aa52-faeb3949fa78.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1318</articleid>
            <title>Infinity Nikki is getting a big update this week, but will that be enough to turn its Steam review rating around?</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/infinity-nikki-update-1-6-playful-season</link>
            <description>Infinity Nikki, the visually impressive, open-world dress-up game that came out late last year, continues to grow with new updates. The game's latest, arriving this Friday, June 13, is one of its biggest, kicking off a new seasonal chapter. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-11</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\d7a6ac81-dfe4-4614-a4db-47d8dfaa06eb.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1319</articleid>
            <title>Your character's attribute letter grades in Elden Ring Nightreign don't really mean much, but you can still use them to your advantage</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-character-attributes-letter-grades-misleading</link>
            <description>Elden Ring Nightreign is, at its core, an RPG with character stats that grow each time you level up. Because of the rapid pace of runs, however, FromSoftware simplified that process and turned it into a one-button affair. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-11</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\f25582c8-1dee-48c3-8fe1-b0827cc466ac.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1320</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign's latest patch casually nerfs a couple of things, but the Demon Merchant will now spawn when they should</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-patch-1-01-2-details</link>
            <description>Earlier today, Elden Ring Nightreign servers went offline for an hour of maintenance to prepare for the release of a new patch. This one is on the smaller size, bearing the version number 1.01.2, so you know its not going to be massive. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-10</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\b4fec1d2-4978-4206-824f-9239cc86819c.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1321</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign players are currently obsessed with an ultra-rare item they believe hides a major secret</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-rare-item-cord-end-secret-hunt</link>
            <description>It wouldnt be a FromSoftware game without some deep, deep lore, and secrets that send you down rabbit holes, and it looks like Elden Ring Nightreign players have come across the first one of those in the co-op game. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-10</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\14a566fd-de92-46eb-8df7-dfa4326a50c9.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1322</articleid>
            <title>Few trailers were as cool as Stranger Than Heaven's Summer Game Fest reveal, and not just because the Yakuza dev's DNA is all over it</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/stranger-than-heaven-project-century-reveal-ryu-ga-gotoku-studio</link>
            <description>Though you may not vibe with every one of their games, its hard to deny that the people behind the Yakuza/Like a Dragon series have an abundant sense of style. Its not every year, however, we get a new franchise from the legendary Ryu Ga Gotoku Studio, but damn if this next title doesnt look special. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-09</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\7861f7cc-3af9-4c2f-9716-9c9c4a29e29e.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1323</articleid>
            <title>The Blood of Dawnwalker is vampire Witcher, and it looks rad in its latest gameplay trailer</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/the-blood-of-dawnwalker-xbox-showcase-gameplay-vampire-witcher</link>
            <description>The Blood of Dawnwalker is a title many fans of The Witcher series have had an eye on even before it was given its name. Thats because it comes from Rebel Wolves, a team of CD Projekt Red veterans, and one that revealed its presence back in 2022. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-09</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\63773250-8a11-4fac-a220-488602b5d47f.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1324</articleid>
            <title>inZOI's May update finally gets June release date - here's what to expect</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/inzoi-june-major-update-details-release-date</link>
            <description>The next major gameplay update for inZOI, Kraftons very successful life sim (basically a modern The Sims), was initially set to arrive in May. However, it kept getting pushed back, so much so that it's already June, and it has yet to arrive. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-09</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\26551806-af15-4491-ba3d-be5e19319591.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1325</articleid>
            <title>Paralives, the long-anticipated indie Sims-like, finally announces an early access release date, adding to 2025's already packed life sim line-up</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/paralives-early-access-release-date-announced</link>
            <description>It's been almost exactly six years since developer Alex Mass (of PewDiePie's Tuber Simulator fame) announced his indie life sim Paralives; now, the game finally has an early access release date, courtesy of its appearance at last night's PC Gaming Show at Summer Game Fest. And, as promised, it's going to be coming out this year  although you're going to have to wait until December 8 to get your hands on this painterly Sims-like. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-09</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\ca08f502-fc19-4387-91cd-62ed1751ac28.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1326</articleid>
            <title>Black Ops 7 is a sequel to Black Ops 2, and it's bringing co-op campaign back to Call of Duty</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/call-of-duty-black-ops-7-reveal-trailer-co-op-campaign</link>
            <description>Xbox couldnt end its summer Games Showcase without teasing the next Call of Duty, which, just like rumours and reports have long suggested, is a Black Ops sequel. Call of Duty: Black Ops 7 is the first consecutive release within the Black Ops series, and it arrives later this year. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-09</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\45476f0a-4901-45f1-b873-d9aa6831a6e8.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1327</articleid>
            <title>The Persona 4 remake is definitely real, and it's called Persona 4 Revival</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/persona-4-revival-reveal-trailer-details</link>
            <description>The days of speculating about, and pouring over Persona 4 remake leaks are over, because the game has been officially announced. Earlier today, we got our first (and very brief) look at an updated version of one of the most beloved Persona games. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-09</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\3b852e1f-8193-4519-b5cf-a353c4f544ad.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1328</articleid>
            <title>Resident Evil 9 is real, arriving next year, and it's looking like it'll be amping up the horror once more</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/resident-evil-9-summer-game-fest-reveal</link>
            <description>The impending announcement of Resident Evil 9 has been sort of hovering around for what felt like months. Insiders have been claiming for a while that we were about to see it at this or that show, but it somehow never materialised - and it looks like today's the day that's finally changed. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-06</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\07ad01b9-ff20-4e43-8c06-adb6143d82f8.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1329</articleid>
            <title>Hopium turns into reality: Arc Raiders will be arriving in October this year</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/arc-raiders-release-date-summer-game-fest</link>
            <description>As part of todays Summer Game Fest kick-off show, what many Arc Raiders players and fans hoped would happen did, in fact, take place. Ever since the end of the second Tech Test in early May, many of those who took part never wanted to stop playing. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-06</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\f5fdcff2-2197-4cf3-ab29-a567264cb7e4.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1330</articleid>
            <title>Zenless Zone Zero celebrates its first anniversary (ish) with major Version 2.0 update and launch on Xbox Series consoles</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/zenless-zone-zero-anniversary-2-0-xbox-launch</link>
            <description>It's a big day in New Eridu as Zenless Zone Zero goes all-in on its first anniversary celebrations, including the launch of Version 2.0, a long-hoped-for Xbox port, and a log-in event that gifts players with their choice of a free S-Rank Agent and free S-Rank W-Engine from the gacha's standard banner, along with 1,600 Polychrome (currency that can be exchanged for 10 pulls on any Agent or W-Engine banner in the gacha), and an exclusive profile title and avatar so you can show off that you were there at the party. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-06</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\a3ac51e0-887f-4d27-89b7-57cfc773eccd.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1331</articleid>
            <title>Summer finally gets going in The Sims 4 with a roadmap, and the reveal of a new expansion next week</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/the-sims-4-summer-roadmap-expansion-reveal-date</link>
            <description>Maxis has, as promised, delivered some news about some of the content coming to The Sims 4 in the very near future. Weve been expecting the June-August roadmap to be detailed this week, and thats exactly whats been revealed. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-06</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\c9c6495a-9def-4b44-9ac6-714f52ed44af.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1332</articleid>
            <title>FromSoftware is finally doing something about quest matchmaking in Elden Ring Nightreign</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-quest-remembrance-matchmaking-fix</link>
            <description>One of the most confusing aspects of Elden Ring Nightreigns design dont have much to do with in-game mechanics, or the loads of key pieces of information the game does not communicate. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-06</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\f5faec6f-401d-484e-aa51-24c650ae692a.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1333</articleid>
            <title>Sony wheels out Ghost of Yotei just to tease a dedicated State of Play for it in July</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/ghost-of-yotei-state-of-play-teaser</link>
            <description>When we first got confirmation of this weeks State of Play, Sonys official description provided little to go on. PlayStations first-party output is quite slim this year, but some of us expected the companys biggest game in 2025 - Ghost of Yotei - to make some sort of appearance. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-05</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\7167a9c2-e46a-4843-9636-74c7eb42dac6.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1334</articleid>
            <title>Silent Hill revival continues with Silent Hill f, set to release on original game’s anniversary</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/silent-hill-f-release-date-revealed-series-anniversary</link>
            <description>Weve had a few glimpses at what Konami has been cooking in terms of the latest Silent Hill instalment, and while things look wholly different to that of the Silent Hill 2 Remake (or even the original Silent Hill 2), theres no denying that the upcoming game looks promising. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-05</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\371c6d5a-0eea-44f4-b153-23a33615bf35.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1335</articleid>
            <title>Look who's back from the dead: Capcom's Pragmata returns with some gameplay, but still no release date</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/pragmata-gameplay-state-of-play-no-more-delays</link>
            <description>One of Capcoms most mysterious projects currently in development has ben Pragmata, the sci-fi action game first announced all the way back in 2020 - five years ago! Pragmata was initially set to launch two years later, in 2022, but it kept vanishing off Capcoms release calendar. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-05</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\25a16c4b-94fd-491e-b2f2-44158ed5f4d2.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1336</articleid>
            <title>Nioh 3 officially revealed - and it's not a PlayStation exclusive, even if there's a demo you can only play on PS5</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/nioh-3-reveal-pc-ps5-alpha-demo</link>
            <description>As part of the PlayStation State of Play, we got treated to the surprise reveal of the next game in the Nioh action RPG series. Its simply titled Nioh 3, and its going to be changing so much of what we know about Nioh. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-05</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\25385e13-19f3-4bf1-b58a-460052f51468.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1337</articleid>
            <title>Violet are utterly transformed on Nintendo Switch 2</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/pokemon-scarlet-violet-nintendo-switch-2-performance</link>
            <description>I can scarcely think of a game as hampered by its performance as the original Nintendo Switch release of Pokemon Scarlet &amp; Violet. I can think of loads of games that perform worse, of course - broken, shattered releases - but I struggle to think of a great game so thoroughly compromised just from how it runs. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-04</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\457d1202-4740-4ad5-977a-dd456ed6dc54.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1338</articleid>
            <title>Christmas came early because CDPR just showed over 12 minutes of The Witcher 4 gameplay</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/the-witcher-4-first-look-gameplay-unreal-engine-5-showcase</link>
            <description>As the developer of one of the largest, most prestigious, and highly anticipated Unreal Engine 5 games currently in the works, CD Projekt Red was invited to the stage of the latest edition of State of Unreal to deliver an updated look at The Witcher 4. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-04</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\b7db3f42-8569-499e-8520-18db6afcaf7c.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1339</articleid>
            <title>After many bet against it, a PS5 State of Play is coming tomorrow with over 40 minutes of game reveals</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/playstation-state-of-play-june-2025-date-times</link>
            <description>Sony has officially announced that its going to be hosting an event in June after all. Its going to be of the State of Play variety, and it will be airing live tomorrow. Sony has, in recent years, made a habit of announcing those livestreams one or two days before the events scheduled date. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-03</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\ff6c95c1-c88c-45e7-8754-68eef7d619a4.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1340</articleid>
            <title>Want to improve your Elden Ring Nightreign runs? You should really stop sleeping on your consumable items</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/nightreigns-consumable-items-are-being-slept-on</link>
            <description>Ive been playing a lot of Elden Ring Nightreign and I mean a lot. At the time of writing, Ive ploughed around 70 hours into chaotic Expeditions and touching Remembrance quests, experimenting with what each Nightfarer is capable of and getting to know the Nightlords all too well. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-03</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\6b90ab1c-1133-40b9-bf33-cdc2faa20767.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1341</articleid>
            <title>Get ready to grind: there’s not a lot going on in the Monster Hunter Wilds Event Quests scheduled for the next couple of weeks</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/monster-hunter-wilds-event-quests-june-early-mid</link>
            <description>A new week brings with it a fresh set of Monster Hunter Wilds Event Quests, just like weve gotten used to since the introduction of the feature a little while after the game launched. This is somewhat of a quiet batch, however, possibly because Wilds recently received a big update that introduced Akuma as a playable character, as part of the games Street Fighter cross-over event. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-03</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\df613caf-9522-4534-91a5-4f81c96d7180.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1342</articleid>
            <title>Duo Expeditions will officially come to Elden Ring Nightreign, as the game passes 3.5 million players</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-duos-confirmed-fromsoftware-big-improvements-in-the-works</link>
            <description>Elden Ring Nightreign launched missing many, many features most of us expect in modern multiplayer games. The co-op action RPG is designed for three players, and thats about the only optimal way to play it. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-03</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\5cdbe1c7-03d6-485a-96ed-8fd2eb33015e.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1343</articleid>
            <title>007 First Light officially revealed as the title for Hitman dev's James Bond game, and we'll see it in action later this week</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/007-first-light-james-bond-io-interactive-reveal</link>
            <description>IO Interactive has officially dropped the first real news on its in-development James Bond game since it was initially announced back in 2020. The game is called 007 First Light, and IO revealed it with nothing but a single piece of art on Twitter. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-03</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\1e9ac2ae-a5b2-49a9-aebd-82ab4167db2a.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1344</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign patch to help out solo players arrives early, but those changes aren't massive</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-patch-1-01-1-notes-solo-player-tweaks</link>
            <description>Elden Ring Nightreign servers are back online following brief maintenance earlier today. During that downtime, FromSoftware rolled out the first major-ish post-launch patch for the game, which does come with a welcome addition for solo players. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-02</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\41ecd608-b9b9-4f0b-816f-a8d8b0ee44cb.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1345</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign players spent the weekend battling the game's online quirks, and its many baffling omissions</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-launch-issues-missing-features-confusing-decisions</link>
            <description>Elden Ring Nightreign is here, and after selling 2 million copies in its first day and becoming developer FromSoftwares second-biggest launch on Steam, the dust is starting to settle, giving rise to thousands of player impressions. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-06-02</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\5b92ce51-4b09-44b7-9fd0-ce5d7df13841.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1346</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign's been out less than a day, and a Souls legend is already showing off a duos mod demo for it, because of course they are</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-duos-mod-demo-yui</link>
            <description>Boy, that escalated quickly. Elden Ring Nightreign, as I write this, has been out less than a day. So, of course someone's already put out a video demonstrating a duos mod for it. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-30</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\38443b4c-45f5-4844-8ccb-55c8374d4e4a.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1347</articleid>
            <title>The battle to play Borderlands Online continues, as dedicated archivists ask for help in pursuit of the long lost MMO</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/borderlands-online-looking-for-help</link>
            <description>The Borderlands Online archival saga continues, with the small group of people hoping to get the game playable putting out a call-to-action for those with coding experience (specifically with software like DNSpy and Unity Ripper) in order to break through the game's character selection screen.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-30</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\eac2ea88-de05-4339-9fb3-9219bc78d333.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1348</articleid>
            <title>Wahey, Helldivers 2 players have seen off the squids and saved Super Earth (for now), cue an over 500 comment-long train of salutes that's still growing</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/helldivers-2-battle-for-super-earth-won</link>
            <description>It's over. Well, for about ten minutes. Helldivers 2's battle for Super Earth has ended, with the Helldivers emerging from the siege victorious and seeing off the Illuminate. For now. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-30</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\c91da359-79de-44e2-8cc4-49b08e67ceb1.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1349</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign update offers solo players a helping hand not even 24-hours after launch because cowards cried too loud</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-update-solo-revive-nerf-coward</link>
            <description>Elden Ring Nightreign hasn't even been out for 24 hours, and already the game has been made easier for solo players. Those tackling solo runs will get one free revive during the Nightlord fight that's part of the run, and will get increased rune aquisition the entire time. 
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-30</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\a51c59d4-fdab-45f9-8ddc-eafc173b9a60.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1350</articleid>
            <title>Surprise, The Witcher 3's getting one more cheeky patch ten years on so you can enjoy mod support across consoles and PC for Gerry's big adventure</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/the-witcher-3-one-more-cheeky-patch-cross-platform-mod-support</link>
            <description>The Witcher 3. It's a decade old now. CD Projekt's well on its way with The Witcher 4. However, in a really cool turn of events, the studio's now realed it'll be putting out one more patch for TW3 later this year, finally bringing mods for it to consoles. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-30</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\0031592c-4dfe-40ea-811e-9dff312869e4.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1351</articleid>
            <title>The studio behind Atomic Heart is kicking up a publishing arm, looking to help get more "big and bold" games made</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/atomic-heart-10-million-mundfish-powerhouse-publishing</link>
            <description>Mundfish, the studio behind Atomic Heart, has announced it's opening up a publishing arm it's calling Mundfish Powerhouse. This comes alongside the studio's celebratory declaration that Atomic Heart has sold over 10 million copies.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-30</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\41004e85-7f5f-4d1e-81c8-25a76cebbb54.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1352</articleid>
            <title>Oblivion Remastered just got a full Skyrim-style smithing system thanks to a modder, in case you've missed making stuff by getting very good at banging hot things</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/oblivion-remastered-skyrim-style-smithing-system-mod</link>
            <description>Right, so. Oblivion Remastered modders continue to find ways to pull off really cool stuff despite not having any official tools. The latest interesting new mod to drop adds a whole Skyrim-style smithing system and skill to the game, and it's by someone who'd already blown us away with their faction overhauls. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-30</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\ff3ba034-4ba7-4e0e-aeb0-f43ec9c26afa.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1353</articleid>
            <title>With the Illuminate now on the verge of defeat, Helldivers 2 was just hit with a fresh barrage of Steam review bombing apparently rooted in a Galactic War comms mix-up</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/helldivers-2-review-bombing-apparent-galactic-war-mixup</link>
            <description>Helldivers 2 has been hit with a fresh burst of negative reviews on Steam over the past couple of days, and it looks like the reason for this uptick is rooted in an alleged Galactic War messaging mix-up involving Chinese players keen to defeat the Illuminate. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-30</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\0a92f675-bfe4-48e3-a836-9d80cf19c674.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1354</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign has a killer first day on Steam, but reviews are surprisingly mixed</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-steam-launch-numbers</link>
            <description>The moment many FromSoftware fans have been waiting for has arrived. Elden Ring Nightreign, the studios experimental, multiplayer-only off-shoot is here, having launched worldwide overnight. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-30</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\fbbb7551-2b1d-4e20-8650-97a303a5c303.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1355</articleid>
            <title>EA, fresh from killing a big Marvel game, reassures fans it still has three other Marvel projects it could kill in the future</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/ea-fresh-from-killing-black-panther-reassures-fans-yeah-whatever-dude</link>
            <description>Yesterday, EA announced it was cancelling its in-development Black Panther game, and closing down Cliffhanger Games, the studio making it. But don't worry gang, EA and Marvel have come forward to reassure fans that there are still other games in development that have yet to be suddenly and unceremoniously killed.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-30</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\19f941ef-f6ee-4fc2-a277-c4adfbd91447.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1356</articleid>
            <title>Battlefield fans are convinced something big is happening on June 17</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/battlefield-2025-june-big-news</link>
            <description>The Battlefield community, and general shooter fans, continue to have little to work with when it comes to news about the next Battlefield. The game has yet to be revealed, or even be given a proper title. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-30</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\f94265d8-1022-45fb-ad8e-643ef7efb4d4.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1357</articleid>
            <title>MindsEye studio confirms its map editory bits come from the weird "community-driven gaming platform" that was originally set to host it, clearing up like 5% of the confusion</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/mindseye-everywhere-build-a-rocket-boy-confusion</link>
            <description>MindsEye, the GTA-ish, Cyberpunk-ish action game about fighting killer AI bots that also includes UGC systems that'll let you create your own races and levels actually pulled those systems from the weird platform thingy it was originally planned to launch as part of. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-29</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\a355691d-eaba-414f-8869-47ec6ca1a81c.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1358</articleid>
            <title>Quantum Witch is a story of religious oppression, queer emancipation, and a dancing skeleton that hopes to popularise the ‘plotformer’ genre</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/quantum-witch-interview</link>
            <description>You might not have heard of Quantum Witch, but if youve an affinity for pixel-art platformers with engaging story-beats, meta-narratives, and an array of kooky characters, then you should be all over it. To just call Quantum Witch a colourful platformer with a strong narrative (read: plotformer) is to do it a disservice, though. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-29</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\83c4158e-57fb-4263-9704-9046a105b6d1.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1359</articleid>
            <title>Shuhei Yoshida warns of the dangers of subscription services for video game developers, as I stare soullessly at the five monthly bank charges for games I don't play</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/shuhei-yoshida-game-subscriptions-game-pass-ps-plus</link>
            <description>Speaking to Game Developer, former head of Sony Interactive Entertainment Shuhei Yoshida has outlined his concern regarding video game subscription services like  Xbox Game Pass and PlayStation Plus, especially their potential impact on third party and indie developers alike.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-29</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\6afe26f1-9626-44e4-b399-bb07fdd1032a.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1360</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign gets a pre-day one patch to deliver some cheeky last minute build tweaking before your first steps in Limveld, and offer advice on some PC issues</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-pre-day-one-patch-last-minute-tweaking-advice-pc-issues</link>
            <description>Elden Ring Nightreign comes out tomorrow, May 30, meaning that your wait to sample a thing we thought was quite good is almost over. Before you hop into classic ER to fight one last Malenia battle for the road, it's worth checking out the contents of the game's first patch - Version 1.01 - which FromSoft has handily deployed about a day early. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-29</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\60ced531-2f28-4aaa-a67b-f87055a9cc90.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1361</articleid>
            <title>Only two cities are still standing in Helldivers 2's battle for Super Earth, and Arrowhead's kicked off an extra mission that might heal the player base's biggest divide</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/helldivers-2-super-earth-two-cities-left-bug-mission</link>
            <description>The last stage of Helldivers 2's battle for Super Earth is coming down to the wire, as we all expected, wth just two of the planet's seven mega cities still holding out against The Illuminate. Cue another extra major order to help the major order, and one that'll cater to the folks who've spent the whole squid invasion half a galaxy away. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-29</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\f6e07c5d-d738-4959-802b-bce795fdea00.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1362</articleid>
            <title>Black Panther game reportedly canned as EA closes Cliffhanger Games, resulting in an unspecified amount of layoffs and role switches</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/black-panther-game-reportedly-cancelled-ea-closes-cliffhanger</link>
            <description>EA's decided to go back to the cutting well. Its execs have decided to cancel a Black Panther game that was in the works at Cliffhanger Games, and close the studio for good measure. An unspecified number of people will lose their jons or have to transition to other roles within EA as a result. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-29</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\ebd15c56-f7d4-4504-a23c-0c598987ffb8.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1363</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign's latest trailer uses Bring Me To Life by Evanescence to supercharge its early 2000s AMV energy</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-evanescence-bring-me-to-life-trailer</link>
            <description>A new trailer for Elden Ring Nightreign has been released and it's, uh, an interesting one. Titled the "Bring Me To Life" trailer, it's packed full of gameplay that's cut to go alongside Evanescence's legendary song of the same name, very much like an AMV.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-29</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\7c00947e-75d1-4338-8264-8bb4976dcbf3.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1364</articleid>
            <title>Dune Awakening's creative director speaks on the end game, and how the Landsraad will give key roles to crafter and killer alike</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/dune-awakenings-creative-director-speaks-on-the-end-game-and-how-the-landsraad-will-give-key-roles-to-crafter-and-killer-alike</link>
            <description>As of writing, Dune Awakening just got its final dev stream going over the mid and end game. These large chunks of the experience have been largely mysterious for the longest time, aside from brief mentions of the Deep Desert and the massive community effort required to interact with arguably the game's most exciting feature: The Landsraad system.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-28</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\0eabcf52-34cd-4a14-bd8e-43fce84cc10a.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1365</articleid>
            <title>UPDATE: Wahey, Cyberpunk 2077's sequel has entered pre-production, and is now being called Cyberpunk 2</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/cyberpunk-2077s-sequel-entered-pre-production-called-cyberpunk-2</link>
            <description>UPDATE (29/05/25, 9:00 AM BST): In the investor call accompanying these results, CD Projekt co-CEO Micha Nowakowski responded to a question speculating that Cyberpunk 2 might release around late 2030 or early 2031-ish time by saying the following: 

"I can reiterate in a way what I said in one of the previous calls, which was basically that our journey from the pre-production to the final release takes four to five years on average, so a little bit less than I think what you said in the question. Having said that, keep in mind that each project is unique and there are many variables that influence the final outcomes. So, so I will not uh lead you into specific years, but yeah, I mean this is this is pretty much [what] it looks like."
Meanwhile, CDPR's senior PR manager Ola Sondej has told The Verge that Cyberpunk 2 isn't the game's official title, adding that it "just means its another game in the Cyberpunk universe".
Original story follows: Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-28</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\2417a011-feb3-4f45-82e6-a70f7038c33e.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1366</articleid>
            <title>The latest tease about gaming's latest worst kept secret, Persona 4 Remake, comes from - you guessed it - a pissed-off voice actor</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/yuri-lowenthal-persona-4-remake-tease</link>
            <description>Voice actor Yuri Lowenthal has offered a tease - well, perhaps more of a vicious peeling back of the curtain - about the Persona 4 Remake on BlueSky. Persona 4 Remake, a game that has not been officially announced yet, will not be having him back as the voice of Yosuke, the actor claims. Bummer!
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-28</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\2925adc0-c704-4533-b69f-3268dd54a4dc.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1367</articleid>
            <title>MindsEye is a GTA/Cyberpunk-ish game about shooting AI robots, and its co-ceo claims there's "concerted effort" involving evil bots to make people think it's rubbish</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/mindseye-co-ceo-claims-concerted-effort-against-it</link>
            <description>Yesterday, Build A Rocket Boy - the studio helmed by Rockstar North president Leslie Benzies - showed off some gameplay from the GTA-ish, Cyberpunk-ish, FarCry map editor-ish action thriller MindsEye, which is set to let you shoot a bunch of evil AI robots. Now, BARB's co-ceo has claimed that there's a real life "concerted effort to trash the game and the studio" going on, involving evil bots. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-28</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\0b2adad7-3f66-45be-8860-a58c9892f04a.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1368</articleid>
            <title>Pokemon Presents locked in for July, as Pokemon Legends Z-A finally catches a proper release date for Switch 2 and OG Switch</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/pokemon-presents-locked-in-july-pokemon-legends-z-a-release-date</link>
            <description>Attention all Bulbasaur plushie owners and potential future Bulbasaur plushie owners. The Pokemon Company has officially announced a Pokemon Presents showcase set to take place in July. Plus, we finally know for sure when exactly Pokemon Legends Z-A will be arriving for Switch 2 and original Switch. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-28</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\fd5d3076-da31-4c70-a56d-1254f66504b6.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1369</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign review: FromSoftware's weirdest experiment yet, and its most powerful message to loyal fans</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-review</link>
            <description>Elden Ring Nightreign is weird. But not in a bad way. FromSoftware has taken Elden Ring as a foundation and joyfully experimented with all its individual components to create something new. Something weird. Something great. The result is a small but punchy experience, rogue-like in nature and rough around the edges. It's also, at least to me, a perfect send off for Elden Ring and The Lands Between.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-28</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\60bf358b-79db-45e4-80c2-1cc81e17b250.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1370</articleid>
            <title>The Nintendo Switch 2's latest discourse asks an important question: will your grandparents notice a massive number two right under their noses?</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/nintendo-switch-2-box-tell-the-difference-discourse</link>
            <description>You. You've asked an elderly or non-gaming person to buy you either games or a console before, right? Well, the Nintendo Switch 2's latest discourse is all about whether doing that with Ninty's latest hardware is likely to result in you accidentally getting an OG Switch instead. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-28</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\7deb73eb-f64d-412b-871e-009f65e32383.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1371</articleid>
            <title>UPDATE: With Super Earth on the line, Helldivers 2's developed a glitch that's stopping speedy-inputting players' stratagems from working, but Arrowhead says it'll be fixed "ASAP"</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/helldivers-2-strategem-input-glitch-fix-coming</link>
            <description>UPDATE (30/05/25, 10:30 AM BST): Arrowhead community manager Miitchimus has just announced via the Helldivers 2 Discord server that Arrowhead has issued an "emergency hotfix" to curb this issue with "fast input of stratagem commands not working correctly". Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-28</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\f9391b3d-c4fc-4404-8f94-3dbeaa74e633.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1372</articleid>
            <title>Diablo 4 Masterworking is now less expensive, but only when it comes to materials</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/diablo-4-patch-2-2-2-masterworking-cost-reduction-directstorage-bug</link>
            <description>Diablo 4 received a new update overnight that delivered a small, but effective change to the cost of Masterworking in the game. More specifically, Masterworking items in Ranks 1 through 4 will now be less expensive. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-28</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\1c51e291-8c67-4515-bebf-7775e28bc428.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1373</articleid>
            <title>Nintendo Switch 2 has reportedly ended up in some online folks' hands early, but don't worry, it currently looks to only be "a very nice paperweight"</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/nintendo-switch-2-reportedly-already-in-hands-update-required</link>
            <description>Well, it's happened. The Nintendo Switch 2 has reportedly emerged into the wild ahead of time, into the hands of people on the internet who're keen to make videos showing off the fact that you open the box and boom - there's a Switch 2 in there. It doesn't look like any such folks are actually able to play games on the console though, thanks to an impending update. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-28</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\dc976ac0-57f0-4a34-a40b-541ef1ae2d5b.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1374</articleid>
            <title>Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 sells 3.3 million in 33 days - and this is not a joke, it's your feelgood news of the day</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/clair-obscur-expedition-33-3-3-million-33-days</link>
            <description>Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 developer Sandfall Interactive has announced that the turn-based RPG never stopped selling well. The game, which came out just over one month ago, has now sold over 3.3 million copies worldwide. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-28</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\ce34cea2-4bbb-4394-af4c-bb41ddc0ecd5.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1375</articleid>
            <title>"We are aiming to do it all over again!" Warhammer 40K: Boltgun 2 principal designer chats what's new with the sequel, and the team's love of Malum Caedo kitbashes</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/boltgun-2-principle-designer-speaks-whats-new-with-sequel-malum-caedo-kitbashes</link>
            <description>One of the coolest reveals at last week's Warhammer Skulls event was Boltgun 2, a sequel to the lovingly made blend of Warhammer 40K and retro Doom games. That first game earned itself a place in many people's hearts, a loving homage to two worlds. But now there's a sequel cooking away, and all eyes are on the future.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-27</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\84a05def-5d14-4614-a129-0eb2e1fd9653.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1376</articleid>
            <title>"This is the endgame" Helldivers 2's battle for Super Earth has entered its "final phase", with agonising failure triggering an "all-out assault" on the final four cities</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/helldivers-2-battle-for-super-earth-final-phase</link>
            <description>Time must fly when you're having fun. Or at least when you're defending Super Earth from a huge Illuminate invasion. Helldivers 2's latest major order is the "final phase" of the battle for the divers' home planet that's been raging since the Heart of Democracy update dropped on May 20.  Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-27</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\f548f96e-abe6-4084-a121-dd830c04eaf6.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1377</articleid>
            <title>F1 25's Braking Point 3 delivers more Butler drama than a Downton Abbey battle royale, but I wish it had pumped the brakes a bit more often</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/f1-25-braking-point-3-impressions-butler-drama-downton-abbey-battle-royale</link>
            <description>Warning: Spoilers for F1 25s Braking Point 3 mode lie head Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-27</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\a19868e7-6d0c-4d3c-8712-2c7e063583e6.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1378</articleid>
            <title>This year's Oblivion remasters got you desperate for a more modern Morrowind? Then come Nerevar, Skywind's just put out a fresh gameplay showcase</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/skywind-morrrowind-remake-skyrim-mod-gameplay-showcase-may-2025</link>
            <description>Sure, Elder Scrolls IV: Oblivion Remastered and Skyblivion either already have dropped this year or are set to arrive before 2025 is done. But the people crave more revamps of classic TES games, and the modders behind Skywind - a remake of Morrowind in Skyrim's engine - have just dropped a fresh gameplay showcase. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-27</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\d5657329-5cee-4c3d-aaab-eda3f27f08ee.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1379</articleid>
            <title>Star Wars Battlefront 2 lives, as a massive community return campaign results in a new Steam player record</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/star-wars-battlefront-2-steam-record-may-4</link>
            <description>Star Wars Battlefront II has been granted a new lease of life. With a community-led effort to storm back into a war-torn galaxy, far, far away, players have flocked back to EA's sci-fi shooter in great numbers, breaking concurrent player records on Steam.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-27</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\cc951b1b-f896-4196-9b49-1a2ad97bc1c3.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1380</articleid>
            <title>“What if I was the bad guy?” Oblivion Remastered’s best new faction quests so far exist because a modder was doing evil stuff, and they’re now teasing “a secret project”</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/oblivion-remastered-coldtyrant-modder-interview-evil-faction-quests</link>
            <description>If theres one thing us folks who love a good RPG can never have enough of, its quests. Oblivion Remastered has plenty in its base form - The Elder Scrolls 4 not being short on stuff to do - but of course modders were always going to add to that. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-23</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\28083468-4912-4fc0-882b-2afa9e439bb4.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1381</articleid>
            <title>There's now an Oblivion Remastered mod that lets you eat rocks</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/theres-now-an-oblivion-remastered-mod-that-lets-you-eat-rocks</link>
            <description>Thrempshs npmopw apnn Oblmpmphon Rmphstrpmshrd mphd aphmt etmphing rshks. Sorry, I've finished chewing. There's now an Oblivion Remastered mod that lets you, the almighty Hero of Kvatch and saviour of the empire (well, in the short-term), eat rocks. Leave room for dessert - there are gemstones too. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-23</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\bc4b9791-bf25-4593-bea0-47a89bcebddd.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1382</articleid>
            <title>Eagleopolis has fallen despite Helldivers 2 players slapping up 2.5 billion squids for an opening victory in the battle for Super Earth, leaving six Mega Cities to defend</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/helldivers-2-eaglopolis-has-fallen-oh-no</link>
            <description>Do you want the good news or the bad news first? Well, good news, Helldivers 2 managed to win the first major order of the battle for Super Earth by slaughtering over two billion Illuminate. The bad news? It's not stopped Eagleopolis from falling. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-23</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\54be5e95-5842-4d0b-b5a1-154ee1a9a66d.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1383</articleid>
            <title>Monster Hunter Wilds' Street Fighter collaboration is all about Akuma</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/monster-hunter-wilds-street-fighter-collaboration-details-date</link>
            <description>Capcom has officially announced that, yes, in case all the teasers werent clear enough, the first Monster Hunter Wilds collaboration event will be with none other than Street Fighter. Collaboration events provide an opportunity for Capcom to bring elements and characters from other games into Wilds. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-23</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\99cf372e-3fb0-4b9e-b139-5c9b23945d8b.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1384</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring Nightreign director says Fromsoft "kind of overlooked and neglected" playing as a duo, but 2 player-friendly "post-launch support" is being considered</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-nightreign-director-fromsoft-overlooked-duo-play-post-launch-support-considered</link>
            <description>Elden Ring Nightreign's director says that while FromSoft prioritised getting the three-player and solo experiences the game offers just right for launch, folks who prefer to take on the challenges of the night as a pair might be getting some duos-focused "post-launch support". Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-23</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\ad569db7-1b3f-4f1b-b7f2-3da653cc3719.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1385</articleid>
            <title>The FTC has dropped its lawsuit against Microsoft following the Activision Blizzard acquisition, letting the tech giant loose</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/the-ftc-has-dropped-its-lawsuit-against-microsoft-following-the-activision-blizzard-acquisition-letting-the-tech-giant-loose-for-now</link>
            <description>The FTC has officially dropped its legal case against Microsoft following the American tech giant's aquisition of Activision Blizzard in 2023. Microsoft is now free from scrutiny, and can now proceed with all manner of business shenanigans with Activision Blizzard in tow without worrying about the courts.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-23</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\c7c29fd6-1c25-4e1c-83c7-61354861d482.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1386</articleid>
            <title>Elden Ring live-action movie now confirmed to be on the way from A24 and director Alex Garland, so now we wait to find out which boss gets the Chicken Jockey treatment</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/elden-ring-live-action-movie-now-confirmed-a24-director-alex-garland</link>
            <description>The long-rumoured Elden Ring live-action movie has now been officially confirmed, with production house A24 and director Alex Garland at the helm. Yep, watch out Super Mario Bros and Minecraft, FromSoft is sending a legion of souls-loving nerds after your box office records. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-23</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\6c5fb115-8499-41f4-84bf-3dd6019bf141.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1387</articleid>
            <title>Diablo 4's Season 9 finally lets us fight Astaroth in the endgame, but the rest of what it brings feels like a re-skin of old systems</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/diablo-4-season-9-ptr-patch-2-3-0-details-new-gameplay-astaroth</link>
            <description>Right on schedule, Blizzard delivered a long and detailed livestream covering Diablo 4s upcoming patch 2.3.0 PTR (Public Test Realm). The developer revealed when the PTR will be going online, and what its actually going to include. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-23</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\3e83746a-4b40-4a4d-ba45-5d213ef2539b.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1388</articleid>
            <title>A cult classic gets some love with the Space Marine Master Crafted Edition, launching June 10</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/a-cult-classic-gets-some-love-with-the-space-marine-master-crafted-edition-launching-june-10</link>
            <description>After Space Marine 2 released to a supurb level of consumer and critical acclaim, it should be no shocker that the Space Marine Master Crafted Edition has just been announced during the Warhammer Skulls event.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\e4d69751-920e-4c58-9177-04a703532d59.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1389</articleid>
            <title>Dawn of War Definitive Edition - a modern version of the best Warhammer strategy game ever made - has just been announced</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/dawn-of-war-definitive-edition-a-modern-version-of-the-best-warhammer-strategy-game-ever-made-has-just-been-announced</link>
            <description>This is not a drill, check on the closest 30+ year old Warhammer fan you know. Dawn of War Definitive Edition has just been revealed during the Warhammer Skulls event! A modern remaster of the legendary RTS game, it'll come with all expansions packaged together in a shiny new package, and is set to release later this year.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\d89dfdc6-a98e-46c9-b7ce-5588cde6acf0.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1390</articleid>
            <title>Space Marine 2 is getting cosmetics for sad space vampires and cool bikers, as well as an endless PvE Siege mode</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/space-marine-2-is-getting-cosmetics-for-sad-space-vampires-and-cool-bikers-as-well-as-an-endless-pve-siege-mode</link>
            <description>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2 got a chunky announcement during today's Warhammer Skulls event. Siege Mode, an endless PvE mission type, will be added to the game across all platforms for free on June 26. The pefect option for those wanting to take on the horde.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\5b0caf40-bced-41df-9fee-6d1b064e5c5f.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1391</articleid>
            <title>Warhammer 40,000 Darktide is getting a playable space cop, and a trusty cyber dog</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/warhammer-40000-darktide-is-getting-a-playable-space-cop-and-a-trusty-cyber-dog</link>
            <description>Fatshark has revealed the next class for Warhammer 40,000: Darktide, as part of today's Warhammer Skulls event. The Adeptus Arbites - essentially Warhammer 40K's version of space police - is getting some representation, bringing with them a trusty cyber mastiff companion.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\158c1f77-8793-471b-959d-566c1410941d.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1392</articleid>
            <title>Supremacy: Warhammer 40,000 is bringing a Grimdark spin to the War Sim series</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/supremacy-warhammer-40000-is-bringing-a-grimdark-spin-to-the-war-sim-series</link>
            <description>Supremacy: Warhammer 40,000 has just been revealed at the Warhammmer Skulls event. Developed by Stillfront, the game is a Warhammer spin on the Supremacy epic strategy game, in-development for PC, iOS, and Android.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\0c3a3921-b375-4b00-9abf-9b1abcbf774c.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1393</articleid>
            <title>Praise the Omnissiah, Warhammer 40,000; Mechanicus 2 just got a new gameplay trailer, featuring a short glimpse at a new faction</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/praise-the-omnissiah-warhammer-40000-mechanicus-2-just-got-a-new-gameplay-trailer-featuring-a-short-glimpse-at-a-new-faction</link>
            <description>A gameplay trailer for Warhammer 40,000: Mechanicus 2 has just been revealed during today's Warhammer Skulls event, and it features a special surprise for fans of the newer era of the 40k narrative. The Leagues of Votann, the newest faction added to the tabletop game, are making their video game debut.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\9f12d5d0-9d08-41fd-af8e-9ee3f822b6c1.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1394</articleid>
            <title>Boltgun 2 is real, and it's bringing Doom to Chaos cultists in 2026</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/boltgun-2-is-real-and-its-bringing-doom-to-chaos-cultists-in-2026</link>
            <description>Boltgun 2 has just been announced during today's Warhammer Skulls event! The sequel to the 2023 Doom-inspired Warhammer 40k shooter, it's set for a 2026 release with the bloody and bombastic return of the absurdly strong Malum Caedo.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\48aec25c-782f-4bec-8b2f-34fe2d2b38e4.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1395</articleid>
            <title>Blood Bowl 3 is getting a bloody big update with a new Khorne team</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/blood-bowl-3-is-getting-a-bloody-big-update-with-a-new-khorne-team</link>
            <description>Blood Bowl 3 is getting a new team, though perhaps one more interesting in collecting skulls than actually scoring goals. Announced during today's Warhammer Skulls event, Khorne is making his gorey debut to the field with a new faction, all wearing red, and all out for blood.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\7bc84dec-a5f3-4a44-ad95-5409b53a9a63.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1396</articleid>
            <title>Total War Warhammer 3 teases its upcoming Tides of Torment, as well as a new legendary lord</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/total-war-warhammer-3-teases-its-upcoming-tides-of-torment</link>
            <description>Total War Warhammer 3 has just released a neat little teaser trailer during the Warhammer Skulls event just now, hinting towards some exciting new additions to the Immortal Empires campaign.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\3c06db24-4718-45d2-b981-6c15de8e81be.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1397</articleid>
            <title>After Rogue Trader proved so popular, Owlcat is working on another Warhammer 40k CRPG: Dark Heresy</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/after-rogue-trader-proved-so-popular-owlcat-is-working-on-another-warhammer-40k-crpg-dark-heresy</link>
            <description>Owlcat Games has announced another Warhammer 40K CRPG, titled Warhammer 40,000: Dark heresy. Announced during today's Warhammer Skulls livestream, it's in development for PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series X|S.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\a4b027aa-276c-4403-b5ff-c9ba881a20be.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1398</articleid>
            <title>Embracer Group says it'll put out 76 different games in the coming year, as it ditches friends for a fellowship and spins off Goat Sim publisher Coffee Stain</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/embracer-group-ditchers-friends-for-fellowship-coffee-stain-spin-out</link>
            <description>Damn, the nice little friendship thing Embracer Group had decided to morph into after earning the ire of lots of folks by going hard on the layoffs, closures and sales is no more. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\f5c54e61-39ec-4057-a1f9-a3355b874136.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1399</articleid>
            <title>Watch Blizzard, hopefully, distract you from Diablo 4 Season 8 by showing off what’s coming with Season 9 in dev livestream</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/diablo-4-season-9-patch-2-3-0-ptr-livestream-times-watch</link>
            <description>Blizzard is hoting the latest edition of its Campfire Chat developer livestream tonight. This one is going to be all about Diablo 4s upcoming Season 9. Or, more specifically, its going to cover the patch 2.3.0 PTR (Public Test Realm), which will be opening its doors soon. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\294abe31-c193-421b-98bd-40e4ce66f765.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1400</articleid>
            <title>Helldivers 2 players struggled with Heart of Democracy's massive flying Illuminate Leviathans at first, so naturally they're now surfing them through Super Earth's skies</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/helldivers-2-heart-of-democracy-leviathan-surfing</link>
            <description>Of all the new enemies Helldivers 2's Heart of Democracy update brought in when it deployed players onto the war-torn streets of their home planet, the flying Leviathan might have been the most intimidating. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\c951de1b-4742-4ede-b4fe-c807593bd181.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1401</articleid>
            <title>Geoguessr pulls out of the Esports World Cup following mass protest from map creators and community alike</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/geoguessr-pulls-out-of-the-esports-world-cup</link>
            <description>Geoguessr has pulled out of this year's Esports World Cup following a mass protest from players and map creators alike yesterday. A wave of protest posts filled the offical Discord, and many of the most popular maps were set to private, leading the company's behind the game's CEO to announce the withdrawal on Twitter and Discord.
 Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\31cbec33-3e26-4327-9e92-ac57604db31f.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
        <article>
            <articleid>1402</articleid>
            <title>Battlefield Labs just introduced its most controversial change yet, and the community is split on whether it belongs in the EA’s in-development game</title>
            <link>https://www.vg247.com/battlefield-labs-weapon-class-restrictions-community-reaction</link>
            <description>The Battlefield community is abuzz with discussion about a new mechanic in a game most of them have not played. The next Battlefield Labs test, which only few players have access to, is going to experiment with something that struck a nerve for many, and caused a bit of a stir. Read more</description>
            <publisheddatetime>2025-05-22</publisheddatetime>
            <categories/>
            <games/>
            <picturePath>assets\4d22e0dd-f110-4ea1-b137-c58968755bbe.jpg</picturePath>
        </article>
    </articles>
</articlearchive>
